fedexkinkos.com 2008-12-16

# FedEx Insight - FedEx Ship Manager - My FedEx

FedEx Corporation understands the importance of protecting the privacy of fedex.com users. The information collected is used to market and improve the services we and our subsidiaries offer, to improve the fedex.com web site content, and to contact you with updates to the web site or for other marketing purposes.  

Certain areas of fedex.com, including but not limited to [FedEx® Ship Manager at fedex.com](https://www.fedex.com/cgi-bin/ship_it/interNetShip?link=4&origincountry=us&locallang=us&urlparams=us), [FedEx InSightsm](https://www.fedex.com/insight/login/index.jsp?link=4&lang=en) [FedEx Return Managersm](https://www.fedex.com/ReturnManager/), FedEx Billing Online, FedEx® Global Trade Manager and [My FedEx](https://www.fedex.com/myfedex/go/home?cc=US&language=en), require registration or a password for access. Information obtained from registered users of these areas may also be used for FedEx marketing purposes, and cookies may be used in those and other areas, as is described in this Policy. Information obtained in these areas may also be used in accordance with agreements governing access to and use of the specific areas, including, but not necessarily limited to FedEx Ship Manager at fedex.com, FedEx Return Manager, etc. In addition, visitors to fedex.com may choose to register for a fedex.com Login user ID and password to simplify access to some interactive features on fedex.com. Log file data and other information gathered from registered users of fedex.com are used to improve the fedex.com customer experience.  

fedex.com Login currently provides users with access to [FedEx Ship Manager at fedex.com](https://www.fedex.com/cgi-bin/ship_it/interNetShip?link=4&origincountry=us&locallang=us&urlparams=us), FedEx Global Trade Manager, [My FedEx](https://www.fedex.com/myfedex/go/home?cc=US&language=en), and Simplify My Shipping. Currently, other applications require separate registrations. In the future, FedEx may add other features to those accessed through fedex.com Login. (In such event, previously registered users will not be required to re-register.)  

Please also see the FedEx Service Guide for terms of carriage, limitations of liability, and disclaimers of warranty and general terms applicable to all delivery services and various information used and provided with FedEx services.  

**For more information on this Privacy Policy, please read below.**

  * What information does FedEx capture about visitors to its web site?
  * Does FedEx ask for personal information?
  * How does FedEx use the information?
  * What happens when I leave fedex.com to visit a FedEx linked web site?
  * What is a cookie?
  * Does FedEx use cookies?
  * Can cookies be removed from my hard drive?
  * How do I contact FedEx?
  * Additional resources on information privacy

**  
What information does FedEx capture about visitors to its web site?**

The fedex.com web server uses an extended log file format which captures: date and time of visit, referring address (location from which a visitor comes to fedex.com), type of Internet browser, and visitor's IP address. (Each computer that connects to the Internet is assigned a unique number, an IP address, for identification purposes). The log file does not capture a visitor's email address

**  
Does FedEx ask for personal information?**

Several areas of fedex.com ask for personal information. They include: Online Account Registration, features of Manage My Account, and registration pages for [FedEx Ship Manager at fedex.com](https://www.fedex.com/cgi-bin/ship_it/interNetShip?link=4&origincountry=us&locallang=us&urlparams=us), FedEx Global Trade Manager, [FedEx Return Manager](https://www.fedex.com/ReturnManager/?link=4), [FedEx InSight](https://www.fedex.com/insight/login/index.jsp?link=4&lang=en) and [My FedEx](https://www.fedex.com/myfedex/go/home?cc=US&language=en). This list may be expanded without notice. In the event that it is expanded, additional information may be required. In these areas, your name, address, email address, billing information, and business profile are requested. This information is collected to help us further develop our services, to provide you access to valuable FedEx Internet-based information and services, and to bill you for those services if you elect to use them.  

Back to Top  

**How does FedEx use the information?  
**

The information collected through this site helps us identify the type of web site content our customers value most. We use this information to market and improve the web site and our services. We also use this information to send you email notifications about updates to the web site, and to contact you by other means for marketing and other purposes. Our policy is to not give, sell or otherwise distribute the information collected through this site to third parties outside of FedEx Corporation and its subsidiaries (unless required by law); provided, however, in some cases we may use suppliers to assist us in collecting, using or otherwise processing for our benefit the information obtained through this site. Our practice is to require our suppliers to conduct such activities consistent with this policy and our requirements.  

**What happens when I leave fedex.com to visit a FedEx linked web site**?  

Parts of fedex.com, such as FedEx Global Trade Manager, consist of products and services hosted by third-party businesses. When you leave fedex.com to visit one of these sites, the only information transferred to the third-party is the fact that you came from fedex.com (the referring address). This practice allows the third-party to monitor its own web site traffic, but does not provide them with any information about you. FedEx is not responsible or liable for the independent privacy policies of our third-party sites. You should consult the privacy policies at those sites to determine how your information may be used.  

Back to Top  

**What is a cookie?  
**

A cookie is a series of data characters that, when programmed into a web site, is placed by the web server into the browser's application folder on your computer. Once placed onto your machine, the cookie will allow the web site to "recognize" you as a unique individual.  

**Does FedEx use cookies?  
**

Cookies are used to achieve two goals. The first is to provide FedEx with the capability to personalize information for certain segments of its customer base. Secondly, in some instances, cookies are used to allow FedEx the opportunity to associate individual customers with their information profiles. For example, through the use of cookies, fedex.com Login can "remember" your user ID when you login to FedEx Ship Manager at fedex.com on your computer.  

**Can cookies be removed from my hard drive?**  

Yes, cookies can be removed from your hard drive. Also, depending on what type of web browser and what browser version you are using, you may be able to change the properties on your cookie file so that cookies are not used or saved. Please check with your browser provider for more information on removing cookies.  

**How do I contact FedEx?  
**

Our postal address is:  
FedEx Corporation  
P.O. Box 727   
Memphis, TN 38194-1062

We can be reached via email at [webmaster@fedex.com](mailto:webmaster@fedex.com) or by telephone at .  

**Additional resources on information privacy  
**

The [Electronic Privacy Information Center](http://www.epic.org/) focuses public attention on emerging civil liberties issues relating to the National Information Infrastructure. [EPIC Alert](http://www.epic.org/alert/) is the online newsletter of the Electronic Privacy Information Center in Washington, DC. The newsletter is bi-weekly and covers issues related to privacy and civil liberties in the information age.  

FedEx reserves the right to amend the Privacy Policy at any time with or without notice. Please check back frequently in the event of changes.  

Your use of fedex.com constitutes your agreement to this Privacy Policy.  

Back to Top
